<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Who am I?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Who am I?</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:34:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Education</title>
            <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my_education/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:34:26 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my_education/</guid>
            <description>Pre college accolades
AP Exams I scored a 5 on before college
- AP Computer Science A - AP Calculus AB - AP Calculus BC - AP German German Language Awards
- 2019: National German Exam level 2 (ATG) Gold Presidential Honor Roll - 2020: National German Exam level 3 (ATG) Gold Presidential Honor Roll - 2021: German DSD-2 written test: first part: top score Deutsches Sprachdiplom - 2022: National German Exam level 4 (ATG) Gold Diploma - 2022: German DSD-2 spoken test second part: top score Deutsches Sprachdiplom Certifications</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Pre college accolades</strong></p>
<p>AP Exams I scored a 5 on before college</p>
<pre><code>- AP Computer Science A  

- AP Calculus AB

- AP Calculus BC

- AP German
</code></pre>
<p>German Language Awards</p>
<pre><code>- 2019: National German Exam level 2 (ATG) Gold Presidential Honor Roll

- 2020: National German Exam level 3 (ATG) Gold Presidential Honor Roll

- 2021: German DSD-2 written test:  first part: top score Deutsches Sprachdiplom

- 2022: National German Exam level 4 (ATG) Gold Diploma

- 2022: German DSD-2 spoken test second part: top score Deutsches Sprachdiplom
</code></pre>
<p>Certifications</p>
<pre><code>- CT conservation license

- US Sailing small boat instructor level 1 certification

- US Sailing teaching and fundamentals

- First Aid and Safe Sport Certification
</code></pre>
<p><strong>Fall Semester 2023</strong></p>
<p>I chose to spend my first semester in college abroad, which offered me the unique opportunity to independently plan my first semester. This gave me the opportunity to travel to central Italy, a part of the world I had never visited, as part of a small study abroad group of college seniors. The experience gave me the invaluable gift of self-advocacy and self-reliance, as the program was entirely hands off and I had to learn to communicate and champion my interests with others with a limited Italian Vocabulary. Beyond that my experience in Italy was amazing, and I am grateful for having gone and having met all the people I got to know there.</p>
<p>Courses: University of Virginia (Charlottesville) Fall 2023 Siena, Italy</p>
<pre><code>- Topics in Renaissance Art History

- Topics in International Relations

- Italian I

- Italian II
</code></pre>
<p>GPA 3.736</p>
<p><strong>Spring Semester 2024</strong></p>
<p>Courses: Emory University Spring 2024 Oxford, Georgia, USA</p>
<pre><code>- Intro to Computer Science II

- Discovery Seminar

- Principles of Microeconomics

- Writing/Inquiry - Liberal Arts

- History of Political Philosophy
</code></pre>
<p>GPA 3.813</p>
<p>*I plan on doing a double major: Computer Science and Business at Emory (or a joint Business/Engineering double degree between Emory and Georgia Tech)</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Work Experience</title>
            <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my_work_experience/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:34:26 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my_work_experience/</guid>
            <description>Summer 2021
In 2021, I lent my help to Nordpan Rubner Holzbauelemente, a South Tyrolean premium-quality solid wood panel producer, as a forester planting year-old saplings on the steep slopes in the Alps where Nordpan Rubner Holzbauelemente sources much of its wood. This experience taught me endurance, precision, and methodology in task completion for a company.
Summer 2022/Summer 2023
I worked as a sailing instructor at Tod&amp;rsquo;s Point Sailing School one of the leading summer sailing camps in Fairfield, Connecticut, USA.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Summer 2021</strong></p>
<p>In 2021, I lent my help to Nordpan Rubner Holzbauelemente, a South Tyrolean premium-quality solid wood panel producer, as a forester planting year-old saplings on the steep slopes in the Alps where Nordpan Rubner Holzbauelemente sources much of its wood. This experience taught me endurance, precision, and methodology in task completion for a company.</p>
<p><strong>Summer 2022/Summer 2023</strong></p>
<p>I worked as a sailing instructor at Tod&rsquo;s Point Sailing School one of the leading summer sailing camps in Fairfield, Connecticut, USA. My priorities and responsibilities at work were to ensure the safety and well-being of all my students as well as teach them the fundamentals of sailing with a lecture and hands-on approach. This required me to communicate effectively with the students and collaborate with coworkers to deliver the best summer camp experience possible.</p>
<p><strong>Spring 2023</strong></p>
<p>In the spring of 2023, I interned at the Fuller Center for Housing of Greater New York City. My work required me to travel to various locations across the state to assist with new affordable housing construction projects, refurbish buildings in disrepair, manage the labor of volunteer groups, and help improve public spaces in underprivileged neighborhoods. This experience was incredibly moving for me on many levels since it allowed me to offer a tangible contribution to the building process, a passion of mine since I was a kid, and to be able to improve the lives of hundreds of residents across New York State.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Who am I?</title>
            <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/who_am_i/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 23:34:26 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/who_am_i/</guid>
            <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a University Student passionate about programming projects that provide value universally and enrich society.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;m a University Student passionate about programming projects that provide value universally and enrich society.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
